To Santa
So yeah... It's Christmastime.
And just take a look around.
I was in town today,
and everywhere I looked,
everyone was all,
"Ooh, it's Christmas Eve!"
To Santa
Right?
Thank you for the super chat.
All those freakin' couples sauntering by, holding hands.
Gimme a break.
What's today?
Just another weekday!
What's the deal with people who get all excited about it?
About this normal weekday.
or whatever
all that nonsense.
And everywhere you look
To Santa
Get outta here with your "Christmas"!
"Take a look at
your own room"?
Well, then.
So, anyway.
GUYS!
IT'S CHRISTMAS!!!
YAAAAAAY!!!
It's Christmas!
Which means... if I keep waiting, Santa will come!
To Santa
"Merry Christmas!" Yay!
So today, I'd like to hold a meeting
about how to capture Santa Claus.
To Santa
For real, though, when I was in elementary school,
I asked for a big brother for Christmas.
I sent... I sent Santa a letter...
saying, "I want a big brother."
I think I was in third or fourth grade? I forget.
But yeah. I legitimately wanted a big brother.
When I asked my mom, she said,
"I think it's too late for a big brother.
But wouldn't a little brother or little sister be nice?"
My mom doesn't actually sound that sexy.
But I wanted a big brother so bad that I asked Santa for one!
And all I got were toys.
Um, that's not what I asked for.
That's when I knew for sure.
There is no Santa.
I asked Santa for a big brother, but didn't get one.
I thought Santa was supposed to grant children's wishes.
Yet he didn't grant
my wish for a big brother.
There's no such thing as Santa.
Yeah...
Boy, I wanted a big brother, though.
"You can't ask for people."
Well, I actually wrote
another letter to Santa.
I asked for a big brother again the next year.
And my mom said she'd mail it so Santa could write back.
And I got a reply from Santa!
Except it was all in English
and I couldn't read a word,
so I tossed it.
@@@@
▲ Full translated video ▲
on YouTube!
Support the VTubers, too!
Okay, I'll read
my letter to Santa.
Dear Santa,
Good evening wasshoi.
It's me, Natsuiro Matsuri.
I've been a very,
very good girl this year.
I made sure to respect girls' personal space,
never teased my viewers,
was loved by everyone,
and gave everyone lots
and lots of love in return.
I don't think anyone else could have done all that.
I will continue to work hard
to represent Hololive's values
and be as angelic and wholesome as Sora-senpai.
So...
hand over the presents.
Nobody deserves presents but me.
I deserve presents the most of anyone in the world.
So gimme.
It doesn't have to be one.
I won't ask for just one.
Two presents...
three, four, even five.
I'll accept them all.
Heck, it doesn't
have to be today.
You can give them to me tomorrow or the day after.
From the humble and not greedy:
Matsuri
Santa,
Merry Christmas.
So, once again...
Everyone!
Merry Christma-ma-ma...
You're kidding me.
Seriously?
I am so done.
To Hell with Christmas.
Seriously.
Like, what?
What was that?
Merry, schmerry.