Hey, hey, boy!
YEAH
NICE!
Nice! Nice!
Yeah yeah yeah!
Yeeeeeeeah!
Yeh-yeah!
See you!
So where are
the cute chicks?
Bring out the chicks!
Whoops, I knocked over the trash can.
Sorry.
My bad.
I plan to stay out of trouble for the first half of the stream.
"You're a natural gangsta."
What? No way!
I'm so pure!
All I want right now is to get a haircut.
You there! With the hat!
Yeah
Yeah yeah
Yeah yeah yeah!
Hey
Hey hey
Hey hey hey
Hey hey hey hey
Hey hey hey hey hey
Hey hey hey hey hey hey
Hey hey hey hey hey hey hey
Hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey!
Put 'em up!
Put up yer dukes!
Hey, where are you going?
I was just heading
that way, too.
Let's go together.
Hey.
C'mon, we're homies,
aren't we?
Everyone's wearing
the same hat.
Is that like, a thing?
Wish I had one, too.
Hey, boy.
Wait up.
Let's go together.
Where's the hair salon?
Oh, here?
Is this the salon?
Wait, are they closed?
They don't look open.
Hello!
Open up...
Oh, here? Is this the place?
Huh? It won't open.
Because it's night?
Why is it night?!
No! Open up!
You meanies!
How come?
Open up.
*BLAM*
*screams of terror*
It won't open...
It wouldn't open...
Huh?
Why?
Why?!
CHANNEL
SOURCE
Look! This thing's so cute!
So cute.
OH MY GOOOOOOOOOOOOD OH MY GOOOOOOOOOD!
I screwed up big time!
There's no way I'm catching up now.
Would you
GET OUT OF MY WAY?!
*tsk*
Whoa! That was close.
Okay, would you
stop dying?!
Hurry up and go!
HURRY!
You could have made that!
Come on!
Stupid!
I've had it with you!
Take that!
It was his fault...
He deserved it!
I brought the car
right up close for him!
What was he
even doing?!
I tried to use the right stick to adjust my view...
But I keep looking at the sky...