Oh, this is Mio's place?
Ah!
No!
I didn't mean to!
N-No... I didn't mean...
No... I didn't mean to...!
It was an accident!
Hang on!
Hold on a second!
Oh, crap!
I just broke out
in a cold sweat!
Wh-What do I do about the lava?!
Where can I find lava?!
Lava...
Oh crap, oh crap!
Just gimme a second!
The Nether!
I should go to the Nether!
Let me just leave...
my iron at home...
Oh, crap!
She's gonna be
so mad at me!
What?
Wait, someone built an aquarium next to mine—
It even has coral!
You've got to be...
Are you serious?
Who built that?!
That's corporate sabotage, you know!
Who the heck built that?
I'll sue you!
That's like building a convenience
store next to another one!
"That happens all the time"?
It's like building an art
museum next to another one!
A movie theater next to a movie theater!
I'll charge them with building
an aquarium next to another one!
*tsk*
I'll get them for this!
Who was it?
I swear.
I'll beat the crap outta them if I ever meet 'em!
Look at this—
You can go inside!
You can even go inside!
That's it! I'll sue
the pants off them!
Ooh, now I'm ticked off!
Seriously.
'Kay, I'm in the Nether.
Why is it so freakin' firey?
There's some lava.
Except...
Um...
Lemme go back
for something.
I need to find dirt!
Mio's gonna be
so mad at me!
"You destroyed my lava, didn't you?"
f
fk
fki
WHAT
HEY
YOU
YOU...
He's trapped in there now.
Got the lava!
Yeah, what?!
I told you, the two of us are finished!
gimme another
chance, babe
Leave me alone!
Okay, now she won't be mad at me.
It's as if nothing happened.
Bonus Scenes
Roboco-shenpai's
house is really cool.
This is A-chan's, right?
A-chan's house?
Pet: Friend A
!
Oh, I got pooped out!
It's honey.
Squishy-squishy.
You know, this kinda sounds like...
I shall call you the sensitive block.
@@@@
Matsuri's channel
Source
More