@@@@
Matsuri's channel
Full outfit reveal
Hair down!
Cat ears!
More
So today...
Well, basically,
I strained my voice.
My voice sounds like crap today,
so please be understanding.
Be understanding, meow!
It's bad though, really.
I sound like an old lady!
I certainly didn't expect
to be unveiling my new outfit while sounding like a grandma.
I apologize for
my terrible voice.
My last new outfit, believe it or not...
was from more
than a year ago.
On November 1st, 2018,
I got my first new outfit...
and none since.
This is my first new outfit since then.
By the way... Oh, yes,
I'm talking about the pajamas.
Let me get nu...
Let me get nude.
Gimme a sec to go nude.
So my pajamas...
Let's see...
There we go.
These are... Oh, gimme a sec.
Here. This outfit.
So basically
it's like this.
This is what my
pajamas are like.
Cute, aren't they?
This is my nude.
Time to show off the new outfit.
It's got a lot of...
Well, I dunno if you'd call it "a lot".
I dunno. But Papa*
worked really hard on it.
* Her character designer @halllki
See, Papa's a pervert.
My Papa is
1) a pervert
2) and a lolicon,
so he understands.
He knows what'll make perverted lolicons happy.
So I'd like to show you what he came up with.
"Please, stop!"
(Papa in chat)
But it's true.
It's the truth.
Okay.
New outfit reveal!
And clap. This is where you clap.
Okay, here I go.
Time to show the outfit.
I'll start from my head.
I'll start there.
From the head.
New outfit reveal!
Ba-da-da-da-dum!
TA-DAH!
First, my head!
What do you think?
Get this!
I have highlights!
Crazy!
Next... I'm gonna do it all in one go.
Here we go!
H-Here we...
Th-Three, two, one!
Da-da-da-dum!
Ta-dah!
Natsuiro Matsuri's
new outfit!
I'm a shrine
maiden!
With highlights!
Well? How do
I look?
By the way...
This thing in my left...
my right hand...
This thing I'm holding in my right hand.
It's for banishing
evil spirits.
It's a spirit-banishing Ebifrion*.
* Her half-lion half-fried-shrimp mascot
If any of you comments something inappropriate,
it has the magical ability
to automatically block you.
The spirit-banishing Ebifrion stick
activates whenever someone makes
an inappropriate comment.
So you'd better watch out.
It's a very handy stick.
Okay! Here's
my lower body.
Everyone's
favorite part.
This is what my
lower body is like.
Shake my hips.
Shake-shake-shake my hips.
It seems other Hololive members
are concerned about
how my waistline keeps dropping.
How Matsuri-chan's bottoms
keep slipping further down,
until her
private parts
(I shouldn't say that)
are almost
exposed.
Plus, it seems Papa has torn open
the sides of my skirt.
So my panties are on full display.
So, what do you think?
Now, just to be clear, everyone.
Hololive approved this new outfit.
I repeat:
Hololive approved this outfit design.
Don't any of you forget that fact.